{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Pre-Fabricated Fireplace Repair Services","appliedActionRules":{"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719":"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719_ctrl"},"categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/40248/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40248,"taskName":"Pre-Fabricated Fireplace Unit - Repair","taskDescription":"Repair a Pre-Fabricated Fireplace Unit","xmTaskDescriptor":"Pre-Fabricated Fireplace Repair Services","matchable":false,"profileable":false,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":303,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Fireplace firepalce faux fireplaces electric","textMessagingName":"Repr Gas Firepl","rolloverLongDesc":"Handle repairs, maintenance, troubleshooting for fireplace units, gas log sets, pellet stoves \u0026 wood stoves. May only service certain brands.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes wood, gas \u0026 pellet fueled systems.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair a Pre-Fabricated Fireplace Unit.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Pre-Fabricated Fireplace Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Fix Prefab Fireplaces","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":31,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":4,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Pre-Fabricated Fireplace Unit Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Pre-Fabricated Fireplace Unit - Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Pre-Fabricated Fireplace Project","urlName":"Pre-Fabricated-Fireplace-Unit-Repair","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Pre-Fabricated Fireplace Repair Pros - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Fireplace,firepalce,faux,fireplaces,electric,corner,chimney,Unit,Pre-Fabricated,ventless,free,vent,stone,prefabricated,stove,wood,outdoor,log,gas,fireplce,surrounds,mantel,Maintenance,Replacement","emcCategoryOid":-12031,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":555,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40248/":{"taskOID":40248,"originalTaskOID":40248,"setID":555,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":6771,"questionDisplayText":"Does your fireplace use natural gas","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Does your fireplace use natural gas","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4737,"questionDisplayText":"Problem Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the problem with the gas fireplace insert? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2758,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Gas smell","answerDisplayText":"Gas smell","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1124,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Broken glass","answerDisplayText":"Broken glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4287,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Not enough heat","answerDisplayText":"Not enough heat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2385,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Fan isn't functioning porperly","answerDisplayText":"Fan isn't functioning porperly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4109,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Needs regular service","answerDisplayText":"Needs regular service","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4299,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Not venting properly","answerDisplayText":"Not venting properly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4738,"questionDisplayText":"Type of fireplace","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of fireplace is the unit inserted in?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3757,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Masonry","answerDisplayText":"Masonry","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2368,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Factory built (zero clearance)","answerDisplayText":"Factory built (zero clearance)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4739,"questionDisplayText":"Venting system","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How is it vented?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4038,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Natural vent","answerDisplayText":"Natural vent","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1930,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Direct vent","answerDisplayText":"Direct vent","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6613,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Unvented (vent free)","answerDisplayText":"Unvented (vent free)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6345,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Through chimney","answerDisplayText":"Through chimney","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6347,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Through the side of the unit","answerDisplayText":"Through the side of the unit","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4741,"questionDisplayText":"Under warranty","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is the unit still under warranty?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":6771,"questionDisplayText":"Does your fireplace use natural gas","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Does your fireplace use natural gas","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4737,"questionDisplayText":"Problem Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the problem with the gas fireplace insert? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2758,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Gas smell","answerDisplayText":"Gas smell","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1124,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Broken glass","answerDisplayText":"Broken glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4287,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Not enough heat","answerDisplayText":"Not enough heat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2385,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Fan isn't functioning porperly","answerDisplayText":"Fan isn't functioning porperly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4109,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Needs regular service","answerDisplayText":"Needs regular service","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4299,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Not venting properly","answerDisplayText":"Not venting properly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2758,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Gas smell","answerDisplayText":"Gas smell","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1124,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Broken glass","answerDisplayText":"Broken glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4287,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Not enough heat","answerDisplayText":"Not enough heat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2385,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Fan isn't functioning porperly","answerDisplayText":"Fan isn't functioning porperly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4109,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Needs regular service","answerDisplayText":"Needs regular service","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4299,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Not venting properly","answerDisplayText":"Not venting properly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4738,"questionDisplayText":"Type of fireplace","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of fireplace is the unit inserted in?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3757,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Masonry","answerDisplayText":"Masonry","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2368,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Factory built (zero clearance)","answerDisplayText":"Factory built (zero clearance)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3757,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Masonry","answerDisplayText":"Masonry","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2368,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Factory built (zero clearance)","answerDisplayText":"Factory built (zero clearance)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4739,"questionDisplayText":"Venting system","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How is it vented?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4038,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Natural vent","answerDisplayText":"Natural vent","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1930,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Direct vent","answerDisplayText":"Direct vent","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6613,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Unvented (vent free)","answerDisplayText":"Unvented (vent free)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6345,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Through chimney","answerDisplayText":"Through chimney","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6347,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Through the side of the unit","answerDisplayText":"Through the side of the unit","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4038,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Natural vent","answerDisplayText":"Natural vent","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1930,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Direct vent","answerDisplayText":"Direct vent","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6613,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Unvented (vent free)","answerDisplayText":"Unvented (vent free)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6345,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Through chimney","answerDisplayText":"Through chimney","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6347,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Through the side of the unit","answerDisplayText":"Through the side of the unit","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4741,"questionDisplayText":"Under warranty","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is the unit still under warranty?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}